(Leonard:)You are not in this relationship.
(Leonard:)I am.
(Leonard:)Ergo, you have no say...
(Leonard:)...in anything that happens
between me and Stephanie.
(Sheldon:)I'm afraid I can't allow that.
(Sheldon:)Pursuant to Starfleet General Order 104,
Section A...
(Sheldon:)...you are deemed unfit,
and I hereby relieve you of your command.
(Sheldon:)General Order 104, Section A
does not apply in this situation.
- Give me one good reason why not.
- Because this is not Star Trek.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)This is banana bread.
(Penny:)This is a door knob.
(Sheldon:)It's my understanding
that an unsolicited gift of food...
(Sheldon:)...can be a precursor to an impromptu
invitation to come in and chat.